marfeel.com 2018-12-23

# Privacy Policy - Marfeel

**PRIVACY POLICY**

MARFEEL SOLUTIONS, S.L. (hereinafter MARFEEL) does not collect any information that enables us to determine your actual identity (“Personal Information“) before, during or after your visit to our Website, other than Personal Information you voluntarily supply to us (e.g. by submitting information on our “Contact Us” page or leaving a comment and your name on our blog).

In compliance with the General Data Protection Regulation UE 679/2016 (GDPR) relating to personal data protection, you are hereby informed that all the personal data that you provide us with through the website [www.marfeel.com](http://www.marfeel.com/) directly or indirectly through your navigation, will be processed by MARFEEL, owner of the above mentioned website, with corporate domicile in Barcelona (Spain), Avda. Josep Tarradellas 20-30, 6th floor; Postal code: 08029 and Tax Number ESB65651259. MARFEEL processes your personal data with the purpose of providing customers with information relating to the social object of the company and about our products and services.

When you provide Personal Information directly to us via the Website or email, it is used by MARFEEL solely for the purpose identified at the point at which you provide the information (e.g. for general marketing purposes or to notify you regarding updates to our products and services).

In some cases, we might send commercial information relating to our products and services based on our legitimate corporate interests. In those cases, you can always oppose or unsubscribe to our data bases for commercial communication purposes.

**WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT VIA THE PLATFORM?**

_Statistical information_

This website collects statistical information from the user by storing cookies on the visitor’s hard drive. To collect this information and submit it to a statistical treatment for MARFEEL, Google Analytics’ services are used; this implies that the collection and storage of the indicated information (hereinafter, the procedures) is done through “cookies” directly between the user’s browser and the Google Analytics server. When the user connects again with this website, the server will recognize the number stored in the “cookie”, as indicated, providing the anonymous information referred to. The procedures are managed and controlled exclusively by Google Analytics.

If you want to know the privacy statement and Google Analytics’ cookies and privacy policies, you can do so at this address:

_Personal information_

We do not collect Personal Information such as your name, address, phone number, e-mail address, credit card information, financial account numbers or health related information unless you voluntarily supply it to us.  We do not link or combine Personal Information with Statistical Information.  
We appreciate that, in certain jurisdictions, an IP address may be considered Personal Information.  As such, we take steps to ensure that the IP addresses which we process does not identify you.

**INTERNATIONAL TRANSFERS AND SECURITY**

In order to provide you with all the information that may be of interest to you about the activities, services and business solutions that the MARFEEL group can provide, we inform you that your data could be transferred to:

-MARFEEL US LLC (USA)

When transferring data outside the Economic European Area, MARFEEL might use software which may belong to companies or whose servers might be established outside the Economic European Area, particularly to the US or to other countries with an adequate level of protection.

MARFEEL only works with countries with an adequate level of protection or the EU-US Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the US Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries. MARFEEL complies with the legal guarantees established to protect the privacy of your personal data. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, please visit:

MARFEEL commits to resolve complaints about your privacy and our collection or use of your personal information. European Union individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding this privacy policy should first contact MARFEEL directly at [dpo@marfeel.com](mailto:dpo@marfeel.com). We will respond to your complaint within 30 days of receipt.

You can oppose, at any time, to the data transfer to MARFEEL US LLC, contacting MARFEEL at [dpo@marfeel.com](mailto:dpo@marfeel.com).

**SECURITY AND STORAGE**

We use appropriate technical, organizational and administrative measures to protect any Personal Information we process about visitors to our Website and/or users of our Platform.

The period of preservation of your data will be that necessary for the maintenance of the contractual relationship and, once it is completed, by the legally established maximum as appropriate. Following that, we aggregate the information and retain it for analytical purposes.

**OTHER IMPORTANT INFORMATION**

If we change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on this page in addition to updating the “Last Updated” date at the top of this webpage.  If we make material changes, we will notify our customers more directly, for example by posting a notification or message on our website or by emailing you prior to such changes taking effect.  We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy frequently to stay informed of the latest modifications.

**YOUR RIGHTS**

At any time, you can exercise your rights relating to the processing of your personal data: access, rectification, erasure, object, data portability and restriction of processing according to the GDPR 16/679 on contacting the following address: [dpo@marfeel.com](mailto:dpo@marfeel.com)

If your complaint is not satisfactorily addressed, and your inquiry or compliant involves human resources data, you may have your complaint considered by the Spanish Supervisory Authority (Agencia Española de Protección de Datos [www.agpd.es](http://www.agpd.es/)), to defend your personal data processing rights.

**HOW TO CONTACT MARFEEL VIA OUR DPO**

If you have any questions, comments or concerns about this Privacy Policy, then please contact our DPO as follows:

E-mail: [dpo@marfeel.com](mailto:dpo@marfeel.com)  
Phone: +34 93 178 59 50  
Address: Avenida Josep Tarradellas, 20-30, sixth floor. 08029 Barcelona
